Alright, the drink that we are about to make is a Claridge Cocktail.
And we are going to serve this as a martini so if you want to set your martini glass to the side with some water and ice in it, that will get it nice and cool for when you're ready to serve the drink.
Now we got our ice in a glass and we're going to do one shot of gin.
And follow that up with a shot of dry vermouth.
And next we will do a tablespoon of apricot brandy and also a tablespoon of triple sec.
Alright.
Now let's shake these ingredients up real well.
We're going to be serving it up with no ice.
You want to make sure you get it nice and cold so that it will stay cold while the person is drinking it.
There we go.
We got our martini glass and a strainer.
Go ahead and pour it in.
Great.
That is a Claridge cocktail.
Bottoms up!